I want to talk about the greatness of instrumental music!
I am Ayune Asakura of Morning Musume。 I am Ayune Asakura of 23.
I am inviting this person as a guest again this time.
Yes, I'm Yaeruna of Tsubaki Factory. This is Yae Runa from Tsubaki Factory.
Thank you very much.
Please continue to join us this time as you did last time.
Last time, I introduced 3 songs by Tsubaki Factory,
In this second part, I would like to introduce 3 songs by Hello!
How did you like the first part?
I didn't think it was a normal job.
It's just a normal talking instrumental.
It's like talking about a hobby.
Yay! Hey, Riley! Did you hear the instrumental? I'm like....
I'd like to introduce the first song of the show.
It is Morning Musume。 It's a joke about selfishness and love.
This song is really a song with lyrics that go on and on without a break.
It's not a slow song, and the lyrics are stuck in that song all the time.
So I didn't really have a chance to listen to the instrumental with the normal sound behind it,
So I chose this song because it is a discovery that I didn't know it was an instrumental.
That's why I chose this song.
This is the B melody at 0:44,
I could hear a musical scale here,
You think the same notes are being repeated, but there are some different notes,
If you listen carefully, you can hear it well,
If you listen carefully, you can hear a bit of a sad sound in the B melody.
The atmosphere of the A melody changes completely from the B melody,
I would like to explain the scale here,
I would like to prepare a certain item here.
Ta-da! Here comes the piano.
I'd like to play a scale for a moment here.
I'm going to play it with the B melody.
Can you hear the B melody?
It's the sound of the B-melody. You may not know where it is, but I'm going to play it with the B melody, so you can feel that they may be almost the same.
I'll try to play it with the B melody, so you can feel that they may be almost the same. Please try it.
If you don't listen to the instrumental alone, you may not understand the sound,
I would like you to listen to the scale again without the piano.
Please do so.
Thank you very much.
Bbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbb!
There is a sound, but it is not like it goes around, or rather, it is like that.
It's more like this than like this.
It's like this.
I don't know how to say it. It's like a beehive.
It's like a hive of bees.
I totally understand.
It's like "rock, paper, scissors.
That's for sure, isn't it?
That's right. That's the kind of sound,
I really like to look for sounds that can be expressed on the piano,
I often do this when I listen to yeast music, and this time I found the scale, so I was able to come to the piano.
I am sure that's true. Piano is not a sound, right?
That's right.
A machine is not a sound. It's a scale.
Everything has a sound.
Yes, there is.
That's why I think it's amazing. It's also a sound.
I've introduced scales in the past, but this item has never appeared before,
If something like this happens in the future, I would like to have her appear again.
So thank you very much.
Bye bye Keane.
I think I just introduced the scale, but the B melody here would normally be
I think I just introduced the scale, but here in the B melody, if it were normal, there would only be a "dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah" sound,
Do you feel like it's a rhythm?
Yes, it is. It's just like a rhythm, but that's not enough to make me dance during the concert,
But that alone makes it difficult to dance or sing during a concert.
So the moment you understand this scale, "tan-tan-tan-tan-tan," it becomes very easy to catch the notes,
It also makes it easier to dance. So when I found this scale, I thought, "This is it,
I could only hear these tones during the concert.
I thought of an analogy. There was an apple.
But an apple is red.
But inside, it's yellow.
You have to see what's inside to taste it.
But you don't see it now, right? If you didn't know the scale.
You were born with a red apple, right?
It's like the red apple has learned this scale, and now it knows what it tastes like.
So everyone should definitely listen to it.
It's amazing, really amazing.
You should listen to it!
You should listen to it.
I would like to go to the chorus.
It starts at 1 minute and 4 seconds into the chorus, and there is a sound called "pokopoko pokopoko.
This sound is often heard in Morning's songs. This sound often appears in morning songs.
When we perform this song in concert, we dance and move around based on this sound,
Sometimes I concentrate so much on this sound that all I can hear is this sound,
Sometimes I dance while listening to the sound of this sound.
Sounds like a lot of fun!
That's right. I think it's pretty easy to understand, so please listen to it. Please listen to it.
I like this sound too.
It's like a swing that makes me feel a certain way.
I like this sound, too.Also this sound.
Thank you very much.
Amazing!!!
Fun!
You put more clarity than I expected.
It's like when you finish moving, this sound also ends.
That's right.
Poco poco song.
This is the chorus,
There is a lyric, "Sadness, sadness, a piece of sadness,
Even with the lyrics, you can still hear this sound.
That's right. I would like you to listen to the song with the lyrics.
Please listen to it.
Can you hear it?
I don't need your love
I'm not afraid of anything.
But I think you can hear it better with the instrumental.
That's why I listen to a lot of instrumental music,
You hear a lot of instrumental music. It's copied, and it's not an instrumental anymore.
You can hear the instrumentation. A lot.
Even if it's normal music, the copied sound is thickened.
It's added on top of it. You can hear it clearly in the snow.
So you should listen to a lot of instrumental music!
Please listen to it!
The song goes back to the intro after the chorus ends, right?
It's a song that goes back to the intro after the chorus,
Morning Musume。 12's Happy Birthday 2,
Kamona, kamona, kamona, gomen wo playasete.
They would say, "I'm sorry, let's play.
When you think the song is over, it goes back to the intro sound again.
Juice Goose's "Potsuri" also has no lyrics,
The sound is the same at the end as the intro, so I would like you to listen to this one as well.
The sound when you go back to the intro was so intense,
The moment it returns to the intro, it fades into the intro sound beautifully.
There are a lot of great sounds in the song.
But the moment you get into the intro, it's so smooth.
Then the accents start.
There is an accent at the beginning of the intro.
We all record that sound with a bang as we pretend to play it,
It's really cool too, so please listen to it.
You'll want to listen to it.
Please listen to it.
The end of the chorus.
It's true.
Yes, it's true.
It's reset in about 2 seconds, and then the intro starts again.
The "selfishness" is that the members line up vertically in two rows like this, and the singer who wants to be loved is surrounded in between. Everyone.
So the choreography is like making a hill by doing it like this.
Until then, we had been doing it like this, but suddenly, it was like, "Dang!
Everyone goes "bang" together.
Yes. It was amazing to see the way they burst into a free dance.
That's amazing.
That's right. The sound is loud. Accents and hits are loud.
It's clear, like it's coming.
It's easy to understand. It's very easy to understand.
And the waves. The waves are very strong.
When you think "bang," it's like that.
That's fun. It's like a roller coaster.
Yes, it is. So I really like performing this song.
That's all for agamakinoma & jokes.
Yay!
Next, I would like to introduce a song called "Manner Mode" by Angeleum.
It was released on December 13, 2017 and is a Blu-ray DVD single.
Yes, I know, I know, I know, I know.
Did you hear this song somewhere?
Yes, I did. I fell in love with it at first sight.
I love it so much.
There's a popping sound from 1 minute 1 second to 1 minute 39 seconds before the chorus,
I like that sound too,
The lyrics of "My Manner Mode" are from the outside looking in.
I can't say it with my mouth, but it makes me tremble.
It's like I can hear you.
Like, I can't say it yet.
I can't say it yet, but the music is overflowing.
Ah.
Yes, it's like that. The lyrics are closed, but the music is overflowing.
Upside-down relationship?
A positive and negative relationship.
I see.
So, please listen to it anyway.
Go ahead!
There are a lot of sounds.
Yes, there are.
It's really cool.
The lyrics, too, but I feel like I can't say the lyrics yet.
You know, the lyrics here.
The lyrics are from when I sang it like this,
Thank you very much.
Just those lyrics,
Like, I miss you, I miss you.
It's a rice.Rice.
It's a lyric of that type,
After that,
I want to hear that one more time.
I'd like to hear that one more time,
Go ahead!
This part is full of honest feelings,
It's full of them.
Here we go.
I totally get it.
It's like a sharp-edged guitar.
This is how I'm doing it,
The lyrics are honest now,
I want to see you now.
But then there's the "tete-a-tete" sound,
That's it,
I'm only sighing.
That's why you were still saying it.
Oh, that's right.
I was expressing my heart's desire to see you right now,
But I was only sighing,
The music was the same as before,
So you went back to the outside.
It's like I didn't fully express my true feelings.
Then there is the part from 1:43,
It's a little different from the sound of the first A melody,
It has a sound like "piroro-piroro-piroro,
I really like that part,
I really like that part.
Please listen to it. Please listen.
Dance.
I'm going to play something different. Now.
Are you okay? I'm glad.
You're really going at it, aren't you?
Yes, yes.
It's like an electronic sound.
And then, "boom, boom, boom, boom," right?
That's what's so great about it! That's what makes it so great!
It would be more fun if you see the lyrics together,
What I'm saying and what the musician is saying are different.
What Manner Mode-chan is saying and what the musician is saying are different,
They are different.
It's already different! It's like...
He's saying it with the same energy.
It's so different.
It's like, "Listen to that.
So, what the lyrics are saying is out of my mind.
But what the musician is saying is her feeling.
Like Manner Mode's feelings.
I thought it was filled with a lot of feelings of concern.
I thought that was amazing.
I love it so much. I love it.
It's like what you're really hiding is coming out in the song.
I love it so much.
The name "Manner Mode" is perfect.
It's right, isn't it?
It's really manner mode.
This is the last song.
I would like to introduce Morning Musume。 I would like to introduce 22.
This is Morning Musume。's 71st single, released on June 8, 2022.
Listening to the tutu tutu instrumental again,
I think it's going to be bad that I can dance and sing with this sound,
It means it's difficult.
That's right.
It is a song that is originally quite difficult to dance to,
But it's not so much a song as it is a song with a lot of thumping sounds,
The rhythm of the song is difficult.
The same sound continues from the introduction,
You can't tell where the song starts just from the introduction.
After the introduction, the song starts playing "choo-choo-choo-choo,
All of those sounds are the same as the intro.
The same sound?
I thought that was one of the interesting things about listening to the instrumental.
It makes me want to listen to it.
That's right.
The first one is at 28 seconds,
This is the introduction, so it has no direct relation to the instrumental,
I joined the band in June last year, and I was very happy to hear the sound of "kakkak",
I joined NATSUA last June,
I joined NATSUA in June last year and accompanied NATSUA for a long time.
I joined NATSUA last June and accompanied NATSUA for a long time,
I was looking at this part of the song and thinking, "kakkakkak",
The "click" part is like a foot clap.
The camera definitely caught someone's feet.
It's like someone's feet are being snapped off by the camera.
I don't know who it was, but I shifted the camera a little bit,
Oh, it's me!Oh, it's me!
That's right.
I think you can probably imagine it, so I would like you to hear that sound as soon as possible.
Please do.
It is now.
I really like the "kakka-kakka" sound. It's a sound frame.
And after that, there is another sound,
It's like a "kakka-kakka" sound, like he's pretending to raise his head.
I really like the way the sounds go together.
So, please listen to it again with a little bit of this cha-cha in mind.
Don't you want me to dance? At the live performance.
Well, it's probably true.
Everyone.
Kakka, kakka, kakka.
Kakka.
Please do it.
Yes, please do it again.
Yes.
I love this place so much.
I love this part so much, I wonder if I'll be on stage too.
The first point is that from the 30th second, the bass note of the melody is engraved in a half-tone rhythm, and then the accent stops again, just like when you stop a record.
And then the accent stops again, just like when you stop a record.
I think there are a lot of Tsubaki's songs, but I really like that one.
You can hear Riley's favorite sound.
Puddle Bond.
I'm so excited.
I'm really stopping it.
He's really stopping.
It's like a rhythm, or this sound is like the main battle,
It's a pretty loud sound.
Everyone is dancing around this sound.
It's like a sound,
It's like they are dancing around this sound.
It's really like that.
It's like the sound of all the pieces being pushed downwards,
It's like the sound of a record being stopped.
Mariya Makino and Chae Haga pretend to stop it like this.
The sound is floating here.
That's right. Hold this,
It's your part,
They line up, grab each other, and put on each other's shoes.
That's amazing.
You grabbed the sound and did the same thing you just did.
It was so cool.
In an instant, they were going boom, boom, boom.
It's like he catches everything and puts it on.
I really like that part.
The use of sound.
I want to try it!
Yes, I do.
The third and final point is the second half of the chorus at 1:23,
The third and final point is the second half of the chorus at 1:23.
Except for the first "wowo," there is a faint "dah-dah-dah" sound in all the other parts of the song.
Please listen to where the "da" sound comes from.
Really?
Dan, dun, dun, dun.
Cool!
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's like a clapping sound. It's like a hammering sound.
It's not coming from the first bow, it's coming from the second mow.
The "dun, dun, dun" is really cool,
It's pretty obvious in the original song, too, with the "dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah,
But when you hear it as an instrumental, it becomes even easier to understand.
Actually, I have never performed this song before.
I'm really looking forward to dancing to it.
Yay! I love it! That's what I'm looking forward to!
That's right.
That's great!
Because, you know, once you know the song, you don't know it.
If you do it before you know the song...
That's great!
That's right.
So, I introduced 6 songs in total for the first part and the second part.
Yay!
It's very deep, isn't it? The instrumental ones.
You should definitely listen to the instrumental ones.
Actually, I was so happy to see the link to my instrumental project on your blog.
That made me very happy, so I was really happy to be able to work with you.
Thank you very much.
I've always loved it too.
When I heard that Riley was doing it, I saw it,
I was like, "I know what you mean! I get it!
I'll be so happy when I do!
Yeah! That's why I'm so glad I got to talk to you!
I was really happy too.
Let's talk about yakei!
Let's go see Yakei!
Let's go see Yakei!Let's go see Yakei!
Let's talk about instrumental music at Yakei.
Let's go to Yakei!
Project has many more great instrumental songs,
Project has many more great instrumental songs, so please listen to them.
So, good bye!
Bye bye!